Hi everyone, it's Aline and I have new items from punkrave.ch I want to show you today.
So I'm creating different kind of goth looks. Everything is black, so I tried to dress a bit more colorful in the beginning.
I have five items I got from punkrave.ch and I have a lot of looks planned, so let's just start right away.
So this is the first item, a cloak and it may look a bit confusing simply hanging on the hanger here.
I'm going to need a panty, fishnet tights and a bra and then I hope it'll be a look.
Preparations have been made. So I'm wearing the panty, the bra, fishnet and already part of the cloak
because it's actually a harness necklace piece and the cloak itself has to be
attached now but I'm going to show you like
I'll make like this first and now I have to figure out how to get this one
attached and I probably need help
Okay, here's the cloak.
And I instantly feel a lot better than I am normally, because I have a cloak now.
It is really, really, really lightweight, so it looks great when you swing it around
like this.
And I can also imagine that it will look really good on a dance floor.
to dance along I guess
so I know that I'm going to take this outfit with me to the Vigotik festival this year
because I think it's a really cool festival outfit
and if the cloak starts annoying me in the evening I can simply deattach it and just use it as a harness part
and these arm rings? I don't know how to call them
You can wear them here at the upper arms like I do or at your wrists.
So the cloak will be a bit lower in that version.
That's the one on the product pictures.
And if you have a look at the product pictures, you should also check out the Piper FCH store.
Because I linked it down below, but I'll tell you if you sign up for the newsletter, you get a 30% discount.
And I think you shouldn't miss on that because 30% is a lot.
And you can buy a lot of great stuff for the upcoming festival season, for the upcoming party season there
Just check it out and have a look
This look is a bit more on the four-leather side. So for the next one, we're going to go with PVC and I have a top and
gloves and pants, so see ya!
Second look and I like this one too because I just like playful, fancy and short PVC outfits.
In this case we have the top here which is the main act so to say. There are several design
features. For one you have buckles here on the straps. I love the fishnet details here in the
cups I'm not so sure about the piercings when I saw it first I was like oh my god no but then I
thought about combining different pieces together and creating different outfits and I was like
okay maybe it will work so I paired it with the PVC pants and also the gloves and I think it's a
cool look it's a look I would call like in my opinion classical Finnish goth
so people often ask me how I got in touch with all this shiny stuff like PVC latex and all the
likes and I'm always saying well it was because of the goth scene I tried to dress according to
goth standards since I was like 17 18 so of course you stumble across PVC I wanted to show you a
second option with the top. So I have a glove here.
Let me check the mirror.
I think I would lose the gloves for this look.
and now cold weather can come
I can also close it, let's see how it looks. But then you of course don't see the top anymore
like this
so it's almost like a completely different look because no PVC top
anymore. Only the pants.
And different. The jacket is also
available in red, which would
also be a really cool option. And
by the way, there is a
male version. So again, check out
the links in the description text
and find out
about the discount.
Link after link in the chain pulling hard at my limbs
The search part is lost now the outlook is growing dim
Praying over wisdom there's nobody left to depart
I am an atom and nothing can take me apart
Second to the last outfit and the punk-rave item here is this skirt.
It's really high waisted and I think it's a great basic skirt.
It does fly a bit if I turn around.
Not as much as the cloak from the first outfit but at least a bit.
The material is like faux leather but shinier so I don't even know what kind of fabric it is.
It feels really smooth and really nice.
I have a second top for this look which I want to show you also from Pancrave.
but I want to try out two different looks with the skirt
to see how versatile it is.
So I'm going to change that.
It almost looks like a dress,
the top together with skirt,
there's no gap here and I also put a harness on top and added some
varninder gloves. So the surface of the top and the back almost looks like the skirt
a bit of shine and all the silver accessories work really well together we
have some in gloves and the harness but also I don't know if you noticed but we
have some buckles here in the shoulder
so I think I prefer this look to the first look with the skirt since the
skirt is high waist you don't notice that this is actually crop top so if I
would wear this with the pants or leggings it would end here and I I would
have the straps from the top wrapped around my belly like I don't know but
it's just a mix of everything strappy here. So if you're looking for some cool
goth clothing, if you're a guy and looking for some cool goth clothing, check out
punkrave.ch because of course I only show women outfits but they also have
cool men looks? Men's looks? Men looks? Anyway thanks for watching this video. If
you head over to punkrave.ch also subscribe to newsletter and use the
discount code and tell me in the comments about your favorite look
because I would have to decide it's a hard one today it really is hard I love
the first outfit and the second outfit and like this combination so I'm stuck
like for every occasion a different outfit I think that would be my choice
today. Also thanks to Punkrave CH for partnering up with me and I think that
is all I wanted to show you today so see you in the next video have a nice day
bye